question_data =  [
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "Ada%20Lovelace%20is%20often%20considered%20the%20first%20computer%20programmer.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "JavaScript%20derives%20from%20a%20later%20version%20of%20Java",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "The%20Windows%207%20operating%20system%20has%20six%20main%20editions.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "A%20Mac%20is%20not%20a%20PC", "correct_answer": "False",
                                      "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "The%20first%20IBM%20PC%20was%20released%20in%201981.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "Time%20on%20Computers%20is%20measured%20via%20the%20EPOX%20System.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "Pointers%20were%20not%20used%20in%20the%20original%20C%20programming%20language%3B%20they%20were%20added%20later%20on%20in%20C%2B%2B.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "%22HTML%22%20stands%20for%20Hypertext%20Markup%20Language.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "In%20most%20programming%20languages%2C%20the%20operator%20%2B%2B%20is%20equivalent%20to%20the%20statement%20%22%2B%3D%201%22.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
                                     {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science%3A%20Computers",
                                      "question": "The%20programming%20language%20%22Python%22%20is%20based%20off%20a%20modified%20version%20of%20%22JavaScript%22.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]

